(Support Admin Watch on kissFlix.co)
Run!
Let's see you run!
I fucking lost again!
It's all your fault!
Still wanna run?
You mortgaged Chun Spa!
Everything is gone!
Please, just let me go!
You've still got this fucking face!
Let me go!
Let you go?
You're my cash cow.
As long as you behave,
there'll be plenty in it for you.
Xiaxia
Hurry, get up.
Are you done hitting?
Stop! Stop it!
I was put up to it!
Stop it!
I'll be gentle.
You're not going to yell at me?
If yelling at you did any good,
I'd have yelled it in your ear a million times.
Sometimes you just have to hit a brick wall
before you turn back.
He said he loved me.
I believed him.
He said he loved the way I used to be.
And I believed that too.
If you jump from here,
you won't die.
It's too low.
You have to jump from there.
The 31st floor.
It only takes five seconds
for your body to hit the ground.
Splat.
And you're dead.
Mind your own business.
Go away.
Why don't you tell me to keep living?
In this world,
is there anything worth staying for?
You're not afraid to die.
So why be afraid to live?
Together,
we either die,
or we live.
Dare to try?
Look.
You got it back for me.
Can I start over?
Can I?
Luoluo,
can I finally start over?
It's okay.
It's all in the past now.
I'll be right here with you.
I'll do exactly as you said.
As long as you let me off the hook.
Get lost.
You're quite kind, Mr. An.
Letting him walk away just like that.
Gambling,
illegal imprisonment,
and intentional assault.
He's already broken the law.
Even if we let him go,
the law won't.
Someone like you, Mr. An,
a pampered young master,
should stick to playing the young master.
Tough games like this
aren't for you.
I might not like
what you had to say,
but,
for what happened this time,
I still need to thank you.
No need.
I did it for Sang Luo.
You
have no right to thank me.
Fine.
About Luo Xia,
thank you.
Between you and me,
there's no need for thanks.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm fine.
Are you okay?
I'm glad you're okay.
Okay.
That's good.
Sang Luo, do you remember
the first time we met?
I remember.
I was dying back then.
Yeah.
You were on your last breath.
The look in your eyes back then,
I'll never forget it.
She's still alive.
Help me.
Help me!
If it weren't for you,
I'd be dead by now.
So I owe you my life.
I'll always be by your side,
and help you get back everything you want.
Since you know the Cheng family is a swamp,
then be careful.
Did I do something wrong?
You still have me.
The dirty work you don't want to do,
I'll do it.
No.
These photos absolutely cannot be leaked.
Do you still want revenge?
For the past three years, you've constantly
been thinking about revenge.
How come as soon as you're back with Cheng An,
you start worrying about all this?
Let go.
I told you to let go!
You failed to protect her three years ago.
You're the one who lost her once.
You have no right to stand by her side anymore.
I'm asking you why.
Even without Cheng An,
we still wouldn't end up together.
Because we were never meant for each other.
Leave Sang Luo.
As long as you can do that,
all the shares I hold will be yours.
How about it?
Made up your mind?
You're not coming back to Korea with me?
No.
You win.
I have a gift for you.
Gufeng Group
Share Transfer Agreement.
Thank you,
Yi Kai.
Call it my despicable selfishness.
I want you to never
forget me for the rest of your life.
And you.
Take good care of her.
Don't give me an opening.
Alright.
I'm leaving.
I should've stayed by your side to protect you,
instead of
letting you endure all this pain alone.
Isn't it fine the way it is now?
After everything we've been through,
I cherish our happiness now even more.
The point is, we're still together.
And we'll never be apart.
Yeah.
Never.
Rest assured,
I'll spend the rest of my life protecting you.
I won't let you suffer the slightest harm.
Everyone,
today's agenda is very important.
We need to select a contestant
to represent Gufeng
in
the triennial wine competition.
Every shareholder
can nominate one contestant.
Let's hear your opinions.
I think
in the last wine competition,
our Director Lin
used "Evening Breeze"
to put Gufeng on the map.
So this time,
she is determined to win.
I'm willing to represent Gufeng.
I recommend
Kista to compete.
Mr. Cheng,
as far as I know,
this Kista
is Sang Luo from R&D, right?
This youngster
asked Purchasing for a huge sum
to buy a patented fermentation technology.
But in the end,
the technology was flawed,
and all the fermented wine was ruined.
You want someone like her
to represent Gufeng in such a major event?
I'll be the first to object.
Sang Luo did make a mistake.
However,
the profits she has brought to Gufeng
far outweigh that one error.
This is Laijin Winery's
sales report for the past three months.
Please pass it around.
The top five wines on the list
were all made by Kista.
Although she lacks experience
and mishandled some tasks,
still,
her winemaking skills
have earned the attention of
many wineries, home and abroad.
Many people even travel here specifically
just to order her custom wines.
Therefore,
her winemaking ability
is unquestionable.
Since
we can't reach an agreement,
I suggest
one vote per shareholder.
A vote is
the fairest
and most impartial way
to select the contestant.
Everyone,
I'll announce the voting results.
It's a tie.
I didn't expect
Gufeng to have so many
people siding with outsiders.
I vote for myself.
Sang Luo,
are you kidding me?
Only shareholders
have the right to vote.
This is my share certificate.
Shares?
My shares in Gufeng are now equal to yours.
Tell me, do I have the right to vote?
Lin Wanmei,
you can't escape.
See you at the wine competition.
Wanmei...
What's wrong?
That bitch Ye Xiaowei...
She stole my spot in the competition!
You can leave Gufeng
and enter the competition independently.
Wanmei,
tell me.
Are you actually worried about the spot,
or that you can't beat Ye Xiaowei?
I can lose to anyone else,
but I absolutely cannot lose to Ye Xiaowei.
Here, Mr. Guo
About the contest slot this time,
I'm counting on you.
Then let me congratulate you in advance,
on taking first place, Ms. Lin.
Thank you.
I've also prepared
a special show for you today.
I hope you'll like it.
Xiaxia.
Long time no see.
Help me out today.
I've brought her here.
I'm leaving now.
Come on, Xiaxia.
Mr. Guo,
let me introduce you.
This is my dear sister,
Xiaxia.
This is Mr. Guo.
Xiaxia,
sit down.
Ms. Lin is so beautiful.
I didn't expect your sister
to be quite a stunner too.
Come on.
Drink up.
Mr. Guo is a friend.
No.
Just have a drink with him.
Let go of me, Mr. Guo.
I'm going to the restroom.
Let go. Don't be scared, sweetheart.
What are you doing here?
Who are you?
How did you get in?
How did you...
It was her.
It was Lin Wanmei.
She paid me
to write the recommendation letter,
so she could enter the wine contest.
Wan Niang was sent by her.
Chu Yan was acting on her orders too.
Shut your mouth!
It was all Lin Wanmei.
Lin Wanmei coerced and threatened me.
She even sold my shop.
She also teamed up with my boyfriend
to ruin me.
Stop filming!
This is for those girls
whose lives you ruined.
They're all in hell now.
Why should you get to live a good life?
Ye Xiaowei.
I'm Cheng An, CEO of Gufeng.
Gufeng Group
was smeared over what happened before.
So
I need to find the truth.
Lin Wanmei,
all these dirty deeds of yours
are being livestreamed now.
What a crazy twist!
Waiting for updates.
This is shocking.
Is this industry really this shady?
Stop reading.
These nasty online comments
aren't worth taking to heart.
You really think I care about this?
They're just throwing a few insults.
People like them
only dare to hide behind their screens.
In reality,
they're just a bunch of
fools led by public opinion,
just spineless fence-sitters.
Watch this.
Open it.
Okay.
You guys don't know?
This Gufeng executive
is actually a fruit farmer's daughter from Taojia Village.
She grew up working in the vineyards.
Who knows what tricks she used
to package herself as
someone from a French wine-making family,
a wealthy heiress.
Her name isn't Lin Wanmei either.
Her real name
is actually Lin Xiaomei.
Holy crap.
I've seen photos of her at events.
She looked so arrogant.
I thought she was real nobility.
Lin Xiaomei.
What a tacky name.
A classmate of our security guard's daughter-in-law
is from this Taojia Village.
People from that place...
Harsh lands really do breed unruly people.
You shouldn't say that.
There are good and bad people everywhere.
It's just that this Lin Xiaomei...
Lin Xiaomei
is truly despicable.
These are all lies!
You only need to know my name is Lin Wanmei.
I was born in Riquewihr, France.
My parents went to France in the 70s.
I am their only daughter.
I graduated from the University of Reims in France.
Our Lin family in France
even has its own vineyard.
I am not some
fruit farmer's daughter!
I'm not.
I'm not!
It's alright.
It's okay.
It's going to be okay.
After discussion among Gufeng's senior management,
we have unanimously decided
to revoke Lin Wanmei's proxy shareholding rights.
You called me here
just for this?
Given your fabricated identity
and the series of news reports
that have caused massive losses for Gufeng,
the company has decided
to terminate your employment contract.
Major shake-up at Gufeng Group
Lin Wanmei dismissed
Reportedly,
Lin Wanmei was involved in multiple illegal activities.
Auntie Ying
Auntie Hong
Ruolin
Cheng Yan
Where the hell did you all go?
Sang Luo
Cheng An
Where are you?
Grandma.
They all left.
What do you need?
Nothing, Grandma.
I'm just borrowing this
to adjust your glasses.
Give it to me.
In the end...
I couldn't hold onto anything.
Lin Wanmei
Look at you now.
This whole family of yours...
It's truly ironic.
A fake heiress
scheming so hard to marry into a fake wealthy family.
Always bragging about
being of noble descent,
having royal blood...
when your ancestor was nothing but
a foot-washing maid for a princess.
Sure enough.
People...
the more they lack something,
the more they obsess over it.
Nonsense!
My ancestors
were indeed from a prestigious family!
Bullshit!
The Cheng family?
A wealthy family?
My ass!
My daughter Xiaoyan
is finally avenged!
I never have to grovel here again
and play along with your charade!
Grandma!
Please don't be mad.
Leaving Gufeng
might not be a bad thing.
In the future,
you'll have more chances to show your skills.
I worked so hard for so many years,
and now I have nothing.
Stop drinking.
You naturally run cold.
Let me make you some red ginseng water.
That was made by Auntie Hong.
It's all gone.
Madam,
do you have time to meet?
Auntie Hong.
You wanted to see me?
Madam.
I've already left the Cheng family,
but since I used to serve you,
I kept thinking about your cold hands and feet.
You must be out of red ginseng paste by now.
So I brought some more for you.
Here.
Try it while it's hot.
See if my cooking skills
have gotten rusty.
Thank you, Auntie Hong.
It tastes exactly the same.
Auntie Hong,
what are your plans now?
How about
I hire you myself?
My goal
has already been achieved.
What goal?
Didn't you
always think the gifts Yanyan gave you
weren't presentable enough?
It's the exact same red ginseng paste,
I just put it in
some pretty packaging,
and you couldn't get enough of it.
Who's Yanyan?
Ms. Lin,
this is my mother's
handmade longan red ginseng paste.
It has no weird additives
and works great for cold hands and feet.
Give it a try.
You mean Chu Yan?
Since you couldn't accept Yanyan's kindness,
then swallow a mother's hatred and pain!
You still don't know
what exactly was in the red ginseng paste
you've been drinking for so long, do you?
With such a perfect opportunity,
you should've just poisoned me.
Such dirty tricks
are beneath even a dog.
What are you thinking about?
My eldest brother is gone.
Cheng Yan...
Cheng Ruolin has been sent away.
Lin Wanmei
has also left Gufeng.
Gufeng and the Cheng family
are just an empty shell now.
I originally wanted to avenge my mother.
But,
Fang Liangxi is in the hospital now,
her fate unknown.
I don't know what to do anymore.
In South Korea,
during those three years I was framed by Lin Wanmei,
hatred was all that kept me going.
I always thought
that only by returning the pain
they inflicted on me,
could I find redemption.
But this process brought me no joy.
I even lost myself at one point,
unable to tell
if I was truly Ye Xiaowei
or Sang Luo.
Luckily, I had you,
and I managed to find myself again.
So, Cheng An,
I won't tell you to let go of your hatred.
No matter what you do,
I'll support you.
But I don't want you to suffer like I did.
I want you to be happy.
Are you here to see if I'm dead yet?
Of course not, Mom.
We've been mother and daughter-in-law for years.
I want you to get well soon too.
Mother and daughter-in-law?
But deep down,
I've never accepted you.
This bracelet
was given to me when I got married
by my mother.
A fruit farmer's daughter like you
doesn't deserve to wear it.
Mom.
Look at the state you're in,
yet you're still talking tough.
Aren't you afraid I'll get mad
and pull your oxygen tube?
Come on!
Pull it!
I'm here today
mainly to make a deal with you.
Looking at your condition,
you don't have much time left.
So,
just consider my proposal.
Impossible.
Even as a ghost,
I will never let you off!
Cheng An already knows his true identity.
Aren't you afraid that to get back at the Cheng family,
he'll hand Gufeng over to the An family?
If that happens,
Old Master Cheng and Cheng Feng's life's work
will end up benefiting someone else.
Look at the Cheng family now.
There's only you and Xie Dongdong left,
just the old and the sick.
Who else can you count on?
Sang Luo is a fraud.
Cheng Ruolin, Cheng Yan...
They never get anything right,
but always ruin everything.
Mom,
I'm the only one you can count on.
I can cooperate with you,
but you have to promise me,
you must make Cheng An suffer.
Don't worry.
I'll definitely protect the Cheng family for you,
and protect Gufeng.
Remember your promise.
Protect the Cheng family.
Protect Gufeng.
It's my Feng's life's work.
This secret today
will be kept strictly
between you
and me.
I think I forgot to tell you something.
Your favorite son,
Cheng Feng.
His death wasn't an accident.